(Leonard:)Hey, Barry, we're in trouble.
(Leonard:)We need liquid helium... does the
department have any we can use?
Sorry, there's a shortage.
(Barry:)And what we do have I need for
my quantum excitation study.
(Sheldon:)But you won't
need much for that.
True, but if it's successful,
I'm having a party
with balloons.
(Leonard:)Come on, Barry,
there's a Swedish team
(Leonard:)trying to run our
experiment before us.
(Leonard:)Can't you spare any?
(Barry:)Be honest... if the shoe
was on the other foot,
(Barry:)would you do this for me?
(Leonard:)Yes.
No chance.
(Leonard:)What are you doing?
(Sheldon:)He said be honest,
so I was honest.
(Sheldon:)Didn't your mother tell you?
It's the best policy.
(Sheldon:)So, what do you say?
(Barry:)Hell no.
(Sheldon:)He could've
softened the blow.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪